Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies Records UA153
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Administrative, 2005 -- 2008; UA153.003; 62 Digital Object(s)
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report June 19 -30, 2006; UA153.003.004.00025; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report July 3 -14, 2006; UA153.003.004.00026; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report July 17-28, 2006; UA153.003.004.00027; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report July 31-August 11, 2006; UA153.003.004.00028; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report August 14-25, 2006; UA153.003.004.00029; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report August 27 - September 8, 2006; UA153.003.004.00030; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report September 11 - September 15, 2006; UA153.003.004.00031; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report September 18 - September 22, 2006; UA153.003.004.00032; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report September 25 - September 29, 2006; UA153.003.004.00033; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
    Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report. This file was labeled September 25-September 29, but review of text revealed that this file duplicates report from October 2-October 6.
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report October 2-6, 2006; UA153.003.004.00034; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report October 9-12, 2006; UA153.003.004.00035; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report October 16-20, 2006; UA153.003.004.00036; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report October 23-27, 2006; UA153.003.004.00037; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report October 30 - November 3, 2006; UA153.003.004.00038; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report November 6-12, 2006; UA153.003.004.00039; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report November 13-17, 2006; UA153.003.004.00040; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report November 27 - December 1, 2006; UA153.003.004.00041; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report December 4-8, 2006; UA153.003.004.00042; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report December 11-15, 2006; UA153.003.004.00043; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report January 8-19, 2007; UA153.003.004.00044; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - 2007 Memo JCCTS Highlights, 2007-01-29; UA153.003.004.00045; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
    Recent JCCTS Accomplishments and Items of Interest
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report February 12-23, 2007, UA153.003.004.00046; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report February 26-March 9, 2007, UA153.003.004.00047; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report March 10-23, 2007, UA153.003.004.00048; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report March 24-April 13, 2007, UA153.003.004.00049; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report April 14-May 4, 2007, UA153.003.004.00050; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report April 14-May 5, 2007, UA153.003.004.00051; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report June, 2007, UA153.003.004.00052; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report July 1-20, 2007, UA153.003.004.00053; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report July 21-31, 2007, UA153.003.004.00054; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report August 1-17, 2007, UA153.003.004.00055; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report August, 2007, UA153.003.004.00056; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report September 1-21, 2007, UA153.003.004.00057; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Jebsen Center Contributions to The Fletcher School, 2005-2007, 2007-10-01; UA153.003.004.00058; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
    Bacow_Bosworth_JCCTSBriefing_10-2007
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report October, 2007, UA153.003.004.00059; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
    Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report October, 2007
  - Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report November, 2007, UA153.003.004.00060; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
    Jebsen Center Weekly Activities Report November, 2007
  - Financial Update for Jan Henrik Jebsen February 2008, UA153.003.004.00061; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
    Financial update for Jan Henrik Jebsen, February 2008
  - Financial reports, 2005 -- 2008; UA153.003.005.00001; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
    Financial reports
- Courses, 2005 -- 2008; UA153.004; 1.2 Linear Feet; 9 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains schedules and syllabi for Executive Education courses, Professional Development and Training courses, and seminars offered by the Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies. Many of the courses offered were one day or one week intensive courses taught by the director of the Jebsen Center, BG (Ret.) Russell D. Howard. The series also contains information on proposed courses.
  - Brown Bag Calendar 2007-2008, UA153.004.006.00001; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Brown Bag Lunch Schedule, 2006 -- 2007; UA153.004.006.00002; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Defeating Terrorism Syllabus for One-Day Course, 2005 -- 2008; UA153.004.007.00001; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Homeland Security and Counter-Terrorism Syllabus for One-Day Course, 2005 -- 2008; UA153.004.007.00002; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Homeland Security and Counter-Terrorism Syllabus for One-Week Course, 2005 -- 2008; UA153.004.007.00003; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Terrorism and Counter-Terrorism Syllabus for One-Day Course, 2005 -- 2008; UA153.004.007.00004; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Terrorism and Counter-Terrorism Syllabus for One-Week Course, 2005 -- 2008; UA153.004.007.00005; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Weapons of Mass Destruction and Terrorism Syllabus for One-Day Course, 2005 -- 2008; UA153.004.007.00006; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Weapons of Mass Destruction and Terrorism Syllabus for One-Week Course, 2005 -- 2008; UA153.004.007.00007; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
  - Budget project training 09/28/2006 [External material], UA153.004.008.00001 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Budget project training 09/28/2006 [Binder material], UA153.004.008.00002 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Professional development courses [External material], 2006 -- 2008; UA153.004.008.00003 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Professional development courses [Binder material], 2006 -- 2008; UA153.004.008.00004 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Proposed courses [External material], 2008; UA153.004.008.00005 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Proposed courses [Binder material], 2008; UA153.004.008.00006 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
- Conferences, 2005 -- 2008; UA153.005; 1.95 Linear Feet; 9 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains reports, correspondence, and financial records pertaining to the inaugural conference for the opening of the Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies as well as conferences on terrorism and counter terrorism studies held by the Jebsen Center. The series also contains information on potential guest speakers for the conferences. The conferences are largely based on Jebsen Center-generated research. Some of the conferences have been recorded and preserved on DVD.
  - Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies distinguished guest series [External materials], 2005 -- 2008; UA153.005.008.00007 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies distinguished guest series [Binder materials], 2005 -- 2008; UA153.005.008.00008 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies opening ceremonies [Binder-front materials] 1 of 4, 2006; UA153.005.008.00009 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism opening ceremonies [Binder] 2 of 4, 2006; UA153.005.008.00010 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies opening ceremonies [Binder] 3 of 4, 2006; UA153.005.008.00011 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder-back material] 4 of 4, 2006; UA153.005.008.00012 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Reconsidering the terrorist threat - What the future holds [Opening ceremony DVD], 2006; UA153.005.008.00013 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Cerberus forum [External material], 2006; UA153.005.008.00014 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Cerberus forum [Binder material], 2006; UA153.005.008.00015 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Fall conference [External material], 2006; UA153.005.008.00016 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Fall conference [Binder material], 2006; UA153.005.008.00017 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Cerberus forum, fall [External material], 2006; UA153.005.008.00018 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Cerberus forum, fall [Front cover material], 2006; UA153.005.008.00019 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Cerberus forum, fall [Binder material], 2006; UA153.005.008.00020 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Cerberus forum, fall [Back cover material], 2006; UA153.005.008.00021 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Strategy for combating terrorism [External material], 2006; UA153.005.008.00022 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Strategy for combating terrorism [Binder material], 2006; UA153.005.008.00023 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - [Women and al Qaeda] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder - front material] 1 of 3, 2007; UA153.005.008.00024 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - [Women and al Qaeda] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder] 2 of 3, 2007; UA153.005.008.00025 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - [Women and al Qaeda] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder] 3 of 3, 2007; UA153.005.008.00026 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Women and al Qaeda part 1 welcome and opening remarks panel 1 [DVD], 2007; UA153.005.008.00027 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Women and al Qaeda panel 2 and closing remarks [DVD], 2007; UA153.005.008.00028 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Women and al Qaeda conference poster, 2007; UA153.005.008.00029 (Box Shared 126)
    Oversized poster located with other oversized materials.
  - [Islam in Democratic Societies] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder - external] 1 of 4, 2007; UA153.005.008.00030 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - [Islam in Democratic Societies] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder - front materials] 2 of 4, 2007; UA153.005.008.00031 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - [Islam in Democratic Societies] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder] 3 of 4, 2007; UA153.005.008.00032 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - [Islam in Democratic Societies] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder] 4 of 4, 2007; UA153.005.008.00033 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - Islam in Democratic Societies Conference poster, 2007; UA153.005.008.00034 (Box Shared 126)
    Oversized poster located with other oversized objects.
  - [Fusion conference background] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder - external] 1 of 5, 2007; UA153.005.008.00035 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - [Fusion conference background] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder - front] 2 of 5, 2007; UA153.005.008.00036 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - [Fusion conference background] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder] 3 of 5, 2007; UA153.005.008.00037 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - [Fusion conference background] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder] 4 of 5, 2007; UA153.005.008.00038 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - [Fusion conference background] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder] 5 of 5, 2007; UA153.005.008.00039 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - [Fusion conference] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder - external] 1 of 5, 2007; UA153.005.008.00040 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - [Fusion conference] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder - front materials] 2 of 5, 2007; UA153.005.008.00041 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - [Fusion conference] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder] 3 of 5, 2007; UA153.005.008.00042 (Box UA153 Shared 2)
  - [Fusion conference] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder - back materials]] 5 of 5, 2007; UA153.005.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Intelligence Fusion conference, 2007; UA153.005.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - [Africa Human Security] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder - external] 1 of 5, 2008; UA153.005.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - [Africa Human Security] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder - front] 2 of 5, 2008; UA153.005.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - [Africa Human Security] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder] 3 of 5, 2008; UA153.005.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder] 4 of 5, 2008; UA153.005.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - [Africa Human Solutions] Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies [Binder] 5 of 5, 2008; UA153.005.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - Countering terrorism in Africa through human security solutions day one, session one, 2008; UA153.005.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Countering terrorism in Africa through human security solutions day two, session one [DVD], 2008; UA153.005.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Countering terrorism in Africa through human security solutions day two, session two [DVD], 2008; UA153.005.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Countering terrorism in Africa through human security solutions, 2008; UA153.005.009.00012 (Box Shared 126)
    Oversized poster held with other oversized records.
  - Countering terrorism in Africa through human security solutions Power Point Presentation, 2008-02-28; UA153.005.009.00013; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
    Mustard background.
  - Countering terrorism in Africa through human security solutions Power Point Presentation, 2008-02-28; UA153.005.009.00014; Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies
    Black background.
- Website, 2003 -- 2008; 2005 -- 2008; UA153.006; 33 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains PDF files of articles originally posted to the Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies website, including articles generated by Fletcher School and Jebsen Center graduate students. The articles are largely about work that was done in the field of counter terrorism by the Jebsen Center.
  This series is arranged as received.
  - Wherein the divide? Terrorism and the future of atlanticism, 2006; UA153.006.010.00001
  - Fight Al Qaeda's plan, not its ideas, 2006; UA153.006.010.00002
  - Connections The Quarterly Journal, 2007; UA153.006.010.00003
    Volume, issue
    VI, 1
  - Beyond boundaries, 2008; UA153.006.010.00004
  - National security implications of Al-Takfir Wal-Hijra, 2005; UA153.006.010.00005
  - Side by side to fight terrorism, 2008; UA153.006.010.00006
  - Josh Gleis: Hezbollah is angry: A time for vigilance, 2008; UA153.006.010.00007
  - Frykter Al-Qaida-wannabes, 2007; UA153.006.010.00008
  - CBRN terrorism post-9/11, 2007; UA153.006.010.00009
  - State and regional intelligence fusion: experiences and best practices in interdisciplinary collaboration, 2007; UA153.006.010.00010
  - Muslim grassroots in the west discuss democracy, 2007; UA153.006.010.00011
  - Strategic counter-terrorism: getting ahead of terrorism Part I: understanding the threat, 2006; UA153.006.010.00012
    The Jebsen Center for Counter-Terrorism Studies research briefing series Vol. 1, No. 1 (December 2006)
  - The state of Jemaah Islamiyah: terrorism and insurgency in Southeast Asia five years after Bali, 2007; UA153.006.010.00013
    The Jebsen Center for Counter-Terrorism Studies research briefing series Vol. 2, No. 1 (November 2007)
  - Strategic counter-terrorism: getting ahead of terrorism Part II: the ideological response, 2007; UA153.006.010.00014
    The Jebsen Center for Counter-Terrorism Studies research briefing series Vol. 2, No. 2
  - Strategic counter-terrorism: getting ahead of terrorism Part III: mass media response to terrorism, 2008; UA153.006.010.00015
    The Jebsen Center for Counter-Terrorism Studies research briefing series Vol. 3, No. 1
  - Terrorism threat in 2008, UA153.006.010.00016
    The Jebsen Center for Counter-Terrorism Studies research briefing series Vol. 3, No. 2
  - The Philippine peace process: too soon to claim a settlement with the Moro Islamic Liberation Front?, 2008; UA153.006.010.00017
    The Jebsen Center for Counter-Terrorism Studies research briefing series Vol. 3, No. 3
  - Styrtrik nordmann mot terror, 2007; UA153.006.010.00018
  - Mattan-Gulan Weekly, UA153.006.010.00019
    This text is completely in Arabic.
  - Preemptive strike: how to fight extremism without firing a shot, 2007; UA153.006.010.00020
  - Dealing with forces beyond our control, 2007; UA153.006.010.00021
  - The Shii perception of jihad, 2003; UA153.006.010.00022
  - Suicide terrorism, occupation, and the globalization of martyrdom: a critique of dying to win, 2005; UA153.006.010.00023
  - The role of "public-private partnership" in maritime awareness and security, 2007; UA153.006.010.00024
  - Integrated operations & training branch (IOTB) quarterly newsletter, 2008; UA153.006.010.00025
    2, 1
  - Integrated Operations Training Branch (IOTB) launches JSOU Press, 2008; UA153.006.010.00026
  - Experts see gains against Asian terror networks, 2008; UA153.006.010.00027
  - Mayhem, myths, and martyrdom: the Shia conception of Jihad, 2007; UA153.006.010.00028
  - Kavkaz center, 2006; UA153.006.010.00029
    Article on Richard Shultz and Andrea Dew that had no title.
  - Public diplomacy: war by other means, 2006; UA153.006.010.00030
  - Familes testify as Cole trial begins, 2007; UA153.006.010.00031
  - Terrorism and weapons of mass destruction, 2007; UA153.006.010.00032
  - Website bundle, 2003 -- 2008; UA153.006.010.00033; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file contains over 2000 files.; 264 Gigabytes
- Additional accessions, 2003 -- 2008; UA153.007; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Digital file spreadsheet, 2003 -- 2008; UA153-021